<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-11-11T16:34:08+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ReviewHuntr.com - The best reviews on the internet.</title><subtitle>ReviewHuntr.com is creating the best reviews on the internet.</subtitle><author><name>ReviewHuntr</name></author><entry><title type="html">Apple Watch Series Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Apple-Watch-Series-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Apple Watch Series Review" /><published>2019-11-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-11-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Apple-Watch-Series-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Apple-Watch-Series-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- product brand --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A smartwatch often provides a simple and easy way to stay connected without needing to pick up your phone, allowing you to answer calls and check your notifications quickly. They are also particularly useful if you want to track your workout routines and any progress towards a fitness goal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They compact everything you need from your phone, but in a more discreet and professional design, ideal for starting and ending meetings on time and returning calls promptly without constantly interrupting work in progress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most recent addition to this line of devices is the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07XQSJ7Q5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Apple Watch Series 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Apple Watches are known for using a wireless connection to an iPhone to perform functions such as calling and texting and can also connect to Wi-Fi network for additional tasks. However, since Series 3 and later LTE Apple Watches can independently connect to a mobile network, bypassing the need for an iPhone after their initial setup. This is a huge improvement, as it allows the user to work separately from their phones, making for a more independent device.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This best-selling wearable device includes an always-on display with energy-saving OLED screen and low-power screen driver capable of refresh rates as low as once per second. Additional new features include International Emergency Calling enabling emergency calls in over 150 countries, a more power-efficient S5 processor, improved ambient sensor, doubling of storage to 32GB, and the addition of a magnetometer, which enables a compass function useful for traveling and hiking trips.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the main advantages of an &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07XQSJ7Q5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Apple Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is Siri. Having easy access to an assistant is amazing. With an &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07XQSJ7Q5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Apple Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; you’ll be able to ask Siri for anything you might need, be it the weather, setting an alarm, or even multiple commands, and it’ll be done in the blink of an eye. Pairing an &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07XQSJ7Q5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Apple Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; with a home kit can be particularly useful, and it will help you automate multiple tasks simply with a voice command. Home kits range from locks to speakers, smart plugs or even light strips that can be controlled easily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second advantage of an &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07XQSJ7Q5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Apple Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is organization. You’ll have your calendar, meetings, timers, and access to different time zones, all so you can correctly plan and distribute your tasks throughout the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07XQSJ7Q5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Apple Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; can also be customized to suit your needs. You can change the watch band and it’ll feel like having a new watch altogether, as the different designs can go from classy to casual or sport. Changing the watch face is very simple, and it’ll help you display the information you consider necessary, all with one touch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07XQSJ7Q5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Apple Watch Series 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; received positive reviews, reaching a promising rating of 4.5 stars out of 5 on Amazon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On this device, the users have commented about the band, which is sturdy and strong but without being rigid or uncomfortable. The design and build quality have been praised, as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Purchasers have found Apple Watch’s ability to track sleep, heart rate and calories very useful. Others have found this device very practical when walking their dog, as this smartwatch foregoes the need for a phone, and it’s easier to use when dealing with a leash or busy hands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Series 5 seems to be a big upgrade when compared to its predecessors. The slightly bigger screen has been accepted positively and new features such as cellular and Wi-Fi have been considered a major improvement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When reading the negative reviews, the biggest complaint was that this smartwatch needs to be activated via an iPhone before its first use. Some users experienced troubles when activating it, while others said it’s very easy to set up and sync with an iPhone. So in this topic, it seems to be more of a technical issue than a problem with the smartwatch itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some said that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07XQSJ7Q5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Apple Watch Series 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is by far the best version of &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07XQSJ7Q5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Apple Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; yet. The always-on display has received favorable reviews, and it’s said that it brings the smartwatch closer to an actual watch. With this new addition, the screen stays always on but dims slightly when your wrist is turned away from you. 
This feature can be turned off if the user would rather not have the screen always lit. However, the always-on can be useful when you need to glance at the time without having to wake it up, as it would be in a meeting or a professional setting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The battery life is said to have vastly improved over previous versions, even with the always-on feature turned on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users had a positive surprise with the quality of the speaker. According to some reviewers, it sounds just like the iPhone 11 Pro speaker, very clear and with a wide range for lower and higher frequencies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users commented that the screen auto-adjusts to light better than previous generations and that the ECG sensor is particularly good and accurate, which makes this smartwatch ideal for tracking general daily activities and workouts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Series 5 has 32GB of storage versus 16GB on the Series 3, this means more space for music, podcasts or apps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what’s been undoubtedly most praised are the improvements to the LTE version and the way it connects to AT&amp;amp;T network, which allows you to leave your phone behind. This makes the Series 5 a worthy upgrade from an &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07XQSJ7Q5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Apple Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Series 3. In previous non-LTE versions, the phone connects to your iPhone via Bluetooth so you have to be within 25 feet of your phone to sync). Because of this, users had to always keep their phone close, which defeated the purpose of having a smartwatch. The LTE version helps you reduce screen time, as you can leave your phone home without the fear missing out on an important phone call or text.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07XQSJ7Q5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Apple Watch Series 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a device you won’t regret purchasing, given its multiple uses and how versatile it can be. Some users go as far as to call it “the best smartwatch ever.”&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>5</name></author><category term="Apple Watch" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Razer Phone Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Razer-Phone-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Razer Phone Review" /><published>2019-11-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-11-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Razer-Phone-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Razer-Phone-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- product brand --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mobile phones have been catered towards the mainstream market since their inception, but today gamers and power-hungry enthusiasts can rejoice. The all-new &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is packed with cutting edge hardware and sophisticated software. With enough power to make any mobile gamer drool, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; hits the sweet spot in regards to price and performance. Coming in at just shy of 400$, it’s much cheaper than the latest thousand dollar iPhones.
Overall, the phone is built with a fairly premium feel. You can opt for a matte black finish, or go with the regal satin finish. The phone has one of the best displays on the market, and hardware to match it. The phone also has Razer’s innovative Chroma software for all your lighting needs. The phone comes with android 9, and a free version of the acclaimed Nova Launcher. The dual front-facing speakers are super loud and feature Dolby’s Atmos technology, which seeks to enhance mobile audio for specific use cases. Overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a solid phone, and ill be getting into the specifics in the next section.
 The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has one of the best displays of any mobile phone. A 120Hz panel allows you to experience ultra-high refresh rate gaming. Most of you are probably reading this review on a standard 60Hz monitor, half as fast as the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;’s panel. Coming in at around 5.72 inches, it’s not a small display by any means. Gorilla Glass 5 ensures your phone safety, being rated to survive a 1.6m fall 80% of the time. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; truly has a world-class display.
 Most people buy this phone for gaming and it doesn’t disappoint at all in that department. If you’re looking for crisp audio to any headset, the onboard USB-C DAC port will give you high fidelity 24-bit audio. If you’re a speaker person, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; won’t disappoint. Dual front-facing speakers provide clean audio, and Dolby Atmos ensures it caters to your use case. If you’re listening to music or talking with friends, Atmos will cater to your needs. The Qualcomm Snapdragon 845 this phone comes with provides the power you need to tackle even the most graphically demanding games. From PUBG to Fortnite, you can be sure you’ll be running them at the highest graphical presets. An onboard vapour chamber provides efficient cooling for this powerful processor. Graphics matter and the Adreno 630 GPU was born to deliver them. Being one of the fastest mobile GPUs in existence, it crushes and mobile game at any setting. Overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; lives and breathes gaming.
 Battery life is important, especially so when you are gaming. Imagine being in a 1v1 situation in your favourite battle total game, only for your phone to power off from the low battery life of your generic phone. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; packs a 4,000mAh battery, enough to easily go through a full day of demanding usage. The USB-C port allows you to charge your phone in no time at all. Powering the powerful display and CPU is no small task, and the battery delivers with flying colours. Few users have any complaints about the impressive battery.
 Memory is something that mobile gamers often overlook, but it matters nonetheless. Modern games are now always a few gigabytes, so it’s important to have space for them. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has a comfortable 64 Gigabytes of UFS storage. This isn’t as big as some of the modern flagships, but the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has a trick up its sleeve. It features a micro SD slot that can hold up to 1 Terabyte of flash memory. Aside from storage, RAM is also important in terms of memory. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes with a nice 8GB of LPDDR4X of RAM, more than enough to comfortably multitask and play games. 
 Gamers aren’t the type of people who require an amazing camera, but Razer still delivered in this department. The front camera is a decent 8MP one, recording up to 1080p video. This isn’t super cutting edge but more of a nice to have feature. The rear camera, however, is a completely different story. It has a dual-camera setup with image stabilization built-in. The first camera is a stabilized 12MP wide shot lens. The second one is a telephoto with a 12MP sensor. The dual-tone flash makes night time pictures a breeze. You can record video up to 4k, fairly impressive in a gaming phone like this. Overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; packs a good camera on a phone that didn’t even need it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, this is an amazing phone catered mostly to gamers. It’s feature-rich and allows you all the comforts of a flagship for a fraction of the price. A 4-star rating on Amazon is nothing to scoff at either.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>7</name></author><category term="Razer" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Razer Huntsman Elite Gaming Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Razer-Huntsman-Elite-Gaming-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Razer Huntsman Elite Gaming Review" /><published>2019-11-10T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-11-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Razer-Huntsman-Elite-Gaming-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Razer-Huntsman-Elite-Gaming-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- product brand --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mechanical keyboards are the pinnacle of typing technology, combining design and functionality into a single product. Mechanical Keyboards have been around for decades now, but the rise of gaming has caused an influx of demand in the community. Nowadays, a good quality mechanical keyboard is the standard for gaming and oftentimes, office work. Whether you type for work or recreation, this keyboard will take your abilities to the next level. Combining some of the latest hardware on the market with some of the most robust software on the planet, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is the perfect keyboard for anyone.
   So you may be wondering, what is a mechanical keyboard? Well, I’d be happy to enlighten you. The Keyboard you probably own right now is a traditional rubber dome keyboard, with a simple rubbery feel on each click. What sets the mechanical keyboard apart is that each button has its own switch that generates a satisfying click. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; holds up to the quality Mechanical keyboards come with, having a very durable body and a professionally braided cable. The body is made of premium aluminium and covered with a matte finish. Overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; holds up to many of the stereotypical Mechanical Keyboard expectations.
   The most defining feature of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is its Opto-Mechanical key switches. Normal mechanical keyboards press on a key switch which goes on to inform the computer about the keypress. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, however, uses light to further increase the input speed. A sensor inside each key switch detects if a key has been pressed by being activated from an internal laser. Essentially, you are typing at the speed of light! The enhanced key switch is rated to survive up to 100 million keystrokes, double the industry standard. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also has 3 dedicated and tactile media control keys that are sure to grab anyone’s attention. These knobs allow for quick and efficient control over any media you could imagine. From music volume to skipping tracks, it can all be done on your keyboard. Overall, the key switches on the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; make it stand out in front of competitors, and truly define this incredible product.
   You may be wondering who exactly this keyboard is for, and the answer is everyone. Even though it is heavily marketed towards gamers, using a comfy mechanical keyboard on those long office hours will improve your mood and efficiency. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; lets you type a fair but faster, so you will no doubt enjoy it. For gaming, this keyboard delivers anything you could need. Quick macros allow for you to instantly act out difficult key combos in your favourite MMO. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; packs a 10 key rollover, so it can register up to 10 keys at once. This is perfect for those of us who love multi-key key binds. Overall, this keyboard is good for just about anyone.
   Razer Chroma is one of the most customizable lighting platforms anywhere. Through the backlighting on your keyboard and wrist rest, you can make incredible light effects. From, having custom effects for every game to syncing your smart lights, Chroma can transfer your whole room into the game. You can even use the hundreds of premade effects available in Chroma Studio made by users like you. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has 38 different lighting zones that you can edit to your heart’s content, the wrist rest has LED underglow, so you can illuminate every inch of your desk.
   Razer Synapse is a powerful macro tool that can turn the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; into a gaming beast. You can make key-binds to simultaneously press up to 50 keys. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also has onboard storage, so your macros will be available on any computer you plug it into. This saves time at tournaments where you want to bring your own macros. A special key exists to enable gaming mode, giving you the options to disable the Windows key and the infamous Alt+F4 command. Never worry about pressing the wrong key again. Furthermore, Razer hypershift allows you to access another full set of keys with the press of a single key. This keyboard truly has it all for gamers.
   We all know that Mechanical Keyboards are only meant for PC’s, but Razer has destroyed that notion with the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. You can now plug your &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; into any Xbox One and use it for basic input. This transforms the traditional notion and adds even more to the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;’s appeal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite Gaming&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a superb example of what money can buy you these days. A top-notch and cutting edge mechanical keyboard with powerful software to go along with it. It deserves its 4.4-star rating on Amazon.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>7</name></author><category term="Razer" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Evga Geforce Rtx 2080 Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/EVGA-GeForce-RTX-2080-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Evga Geforce Rtx 2080 Review" /><published>2019-11-03T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-11-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/EVGA-GeForce-RTX-2080-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/EVGA-GeForce-RTX-2080-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- product brand --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07N889XT8?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;EVGA GeForce RTX 2080&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a top of the line graphics card, offering robust performance for gamers and content creators alike. It is one of the few graphics cards on the market that can truly handle the demands of nearly any workload. Combined with AI-powered Ray-Tracing technology, it has unmatched performance. This &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07N889XT8?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;GeForce RTX 2080&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; edition comes with pre-installed water cooling, so all you need to do is plug it into your array. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07N889XT8?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;EVGA GeForce RTX 2080&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; truly offers a one-size-fits-all solution in the difficult to navigate the world of graphics cards. It has an impressive 3.7 stars on Amazon, so you’ll be sure to get a functional and powerful product. &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07N889XT8?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;GeForce RTX 2080&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is an industry leader in terms of computer hardware, being one of the largest companies in the scene. I’ll be going through the technical specifications of this product and the workload it can handle, the advanced Ray-Tracing capabilities it comes pre-loaded with, and lastly the different uses it has. Let’s get right into the review!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07N889XT8?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;EVGA GeForce RTX 2080&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; can truly handle any workload, from content creation to gaming. Its robust specifications showcase that, and most users agree upon its unparalleled versatility. Most users purchase this card for gaming, as that’s the user base &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07N889XT8?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;GeForce RTX 2080&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; most often markets its products for. There are no complaints about its performance and versatility. Many users say that during demanding usage, the temperatures can get fairly high. Most users report peaks of 85-86 degrees celsius, which is fairly hot. However, using the water cooling this card was engineered to bring temperatures down to a much more favourable state. Overall, this card can handle nearly all workloads thrown at it easily when matched with popper cooling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specifications are what matters in our performance-hungry modern world games. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07N889XT8?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;EVGA GeForce RTX 2080&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes packed with 8GB of GDDR6 RAM, one of the fastest video memory types in the world. This RAM runs at a blazing fast 14,000 MHz memory speed, capable of storing and retrieving information at a nearly unheard of rate. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07N889XT8?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;EVGA GeForce RTX 2080&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has am 1800Mhz boost clock, extremely fast! This card definitely packs a punch, and can definitely handle nearly anything. In the next section, ill be talking about this card’s most revered feature, Ray-Tracing. This card in specific has built-in water cooling support, so all you have to do is plug it into your current loop. This is a lot easier than having to add a water cooling block as some cards require. The all-metal backplate provides a premium feel and enhances the cards overall structural integrity. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07N889XT8?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;EVGA GeForce RTX 2080&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; supports Nvidia G-Sync so you can experience truly smooth gameplay on compatible monitors. The built-in DisplayPort 1.4 and HDMI 2.0 ports are some of the most powerful modern graphical ports. NVIDIA GPU Boost technology is present in this card, allowing you to push your cards to the limit. This card also has an 8-phase power supply to keep your card safe in the event of a power surge or power loss. The built-in 9-blade dual-fan array is more than enough to keep your system cool. Adjustable RGB LED’s add to the card’s gamer aesthetic, leaving a lasting impression on those that view your rig. No user has a complaint regarding the card’s specifications, so you can rest assured you will have a well built and powerful product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ray-Tracing is an extremely advanced processing platform that can analyze environments in real-time and trace lighting to effectively achieve a nearly photo-realistic environment. Graphics cards with Ray-Tracing can perform up to 6X faster and are powered with AI analysis techniques. This cutting edge technology is easily the most powerful processing technique on the market, effectively tracing every ray of light to provide a picture-perfect image. Ray-Tracing also allows content-creators to run vivid simulations for further scrutiny. Ray-Tracing is a huge plus when purchasing a graphics card, and you’re certainly in luck here with the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07N889XT8?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;EVGA GeForce RTX 2080&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gaming is what most people buy this card for, and it definitely holds up. Most users can effortlessly run their favourite games in 4K resolution at the heights of settings. The unprecedented power of this card has pressed many gaming studios to innovate further in their graphics field. Ray-Tracing is finally being adopted in the gaming industry, something they will finally utilize the full power of this card/ Not a single user has had a complaint about its performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07N889XT8?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;EVGA GeForce RTX 2080&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a super graphics card no matter your need. It has all the power you could ever want and has some of the most cutting edge features on the market. Few users have any complaints about this product, so you can be sure you are getting a high-quality product. It is definitely deserving of its 3.7-star rating on Amazon.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>7</name></author><category term="EVGA GeForce" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Facebook Voting Machines Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/facebook-voting-machines-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Facebook Voting Machines Review" /><published>2019-11-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-11-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/facebook-voting-machines-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/facebook-voting-machines-review/">&lt;p&gt;Just in time for a fresh election cycle, a new tech startup says it finally holds the solution to foreign interference in American elections. Nootrusha has invented voting machines powered by Facebook with plans to use the technology in critical state and local government elections. We had an opportunity to learn more about these new machines from lead designer Джон Smith. “We are very pleased to start testing them in the field. There are many important choices ahead. People lose confidence in the system with all these reports of election hacking. The decision looked us all this time in the face. By making the process less obvious, we can help restore this confidence in the election.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These new IoT connected voting machines take voting technology a quantum leap into the future. With never before seen conveniences, features, and security measures. You might need sunglasses when you checkout out the bright new 4k OLED touchscreens that display inspirational messages such as “OBEY”, “CONSUME”, and “CONFORM”. Security is an ever-growing concern in the new digital age, and Nootrusha has added features like facial recognition, non-invasive infrared retinal test, and rectal scanning to help assure nobody can steal your identity or vote. For those that feel the new security measures have the potential for abuse, Джон notes that there are also super cool filters that transform your face in real-time. A cute puppy nose and ears, The Mask from the 1994 hit movie The Mask starring Jim Carrey, and dark mode Justin Trudeau are some of the most popular choices in their usability testing. Nootrusha says they have many more in development with the hopes they’ll be ready for the field trials. A “flappy ears” filter in honor of Ross Perot with a toggle that changes them to Barak Obama. And there’s also the limited edition “stained dress” filter by Monica Lewinsky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nootrusha thinks the updates in their design will help make voting more appealing to younger demographics, which historically have a substantially lower turnout in elections despite being unhappy about the current state of like - everything. Jenny from Fort Lauderdale, Florida, had a lot of praise for the new voting machines. “This is so awesome! I love that it let me register with Facebook. And at first, the security stuff had me worried, but then I turned on the Drake filter, AND I HAD DRAKE’S BEARD WITH A GRILL. It was sooooo yeet. And the auto voting feature is a lifesaver. I tried to look up some of the names, but none of them showed up in Spotify. All I had to do was auto-vote, and it did the rest! It even let me share my Drake selfie on Instagram.”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Джон says the new auto-voting option helps streamline the voting process more efficiently than any other solutions available on the market. Джон added, “Companies already track all of your personal information and manipulate your entire existence to influence your decisions. Most people can’t afford free will, and being informed isn’t practical. We’ve managed to streamline the process. We can analyze your social media account to make the same decisions that you would have made yourself. Of course, the more often you use Facebook, the more accurate the results will be. Therefore, we strongly recommend that voters spend as much time using the app as possible. Your Facebook app usage might even be a great measure of patriotism when we expand the program”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He went on to explain how the auto-voting feature uses proprietary machine learning and artificial intelligence algorithms to determine the selections it makes for you. “First, we take all of the content that you and your friends share on social media and completely filter them out of the data. We do this to prevent personal bias impacting the results. That leaves us mostly with advertisements, but it’s good enough. Based on that content, we can easily choose the candidates you will resonate with the most. It could be the latest elderly jingoist running for president or some new up and coming representative with grand ideas for change and few plans to practically see them through. The system is very flexible and responds well across the political spectrum. We are helping voters spend more time relishing in the election spectacles and less time worrying about where their vote goes.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not everyone is excited about the changes, though. A representative from Mosourri’s 7th district says the new Facebook integration in the voting machines poses a danger for young voters. “We already have plenty of ways to mislead, I mean, inform voters. TV, radio, and newspapers have worked perfectly fine for decades. Mr. Facebook has no business trying to get inside the machines we use to vote. And as concerned parents, we’re confident these social media trends will go away if we can make them illegal. They encourage kids to spend too much time on their smartphones instead of watching TV or reading newspapers. We shouldn’t allow it. There’s enormous potential for abuse. Why isn’t anyone thinking of the children?! What if foreign influences start taking advantage of young impressionable voters before we do? Even worse, these social medias are hurting our local economy and continue to disrupt important businesses. Our only newspaper shut down earlier this year, and they were the primary supporter of my campaign. They’ve been advising me since the beginning. How am I supposed to know what laws I should pass now? Americans everywhere should be outraged that these techno loonies are opening a pandora’s box of harm to the very fabric of our country.”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There hasn’t been a lot of reaction to the representative’s warnings since he doesn’t have a Facebook account to share them. Still, others who aren’t super lame have raised similar concerns with the technology. But Джон assures everyone that their tech is developed right here in the heartland of America, Silicon Valley, to help Americans remove all the stressful parts of the election season. Allowing them to focus on the parts of it they love. Джон handed us a laser pointer which projected an image of the United States seal with the eagle modified to include a large erect cock and balls. He then drank from a flask of what smelled like vodka and took an uncomfortably long drag from his cigarette.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Джон hopes to see their efforts help to restore peoples faith in elections, without really changing anything.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>0</name></author><category term="sharkbait" /><summary type="html">Just in time for a fresh election cycle, a new tech startup says it finally holds the solution to foreign interference in American elections. Nootrusha has invented voting machines powered by Facebook with plans to use the technology in critical state and local government elections. We had an opportunity to learn more about these new machines from lead designer Джон Smith. “We are very pleased to start testing them in the field. There are many important choices ahead. People lose confidence in the system with all these reports of election hacking. The decision looked us all this time in the face. By making the process less obvious, we can help restore this confidence in the election.”</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Real Life Joker Costume Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/real-life-joker-costume-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Real Life Joker Costume Review" /><published>2019-10-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/real-life-joker-costume-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/real-life-joker-costume-review/">&lt;p&gt;We live in a society that loves Halloween. We all could agree that Halloween is easily one of the coolest parts of the year. You are getting free candy from your neighbors for no reason at all, freaking out because you don’t find the perfect idea for your costume this year, parents letting their children play with their friends, at night, with lots of disguised people all around. Michael Jackson’s private heaven. But this year, you don’t have to worry about which one could be the ideal costume for you. Costume &amp;amp; Customs is ready to help you be the laugh of your office’s Halloween Party this October.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the world’s most highly regarded costume designer and manufacturer brings you the brand new Real Life Joker Costume Equipment. Taking advantage of the popularity of this year’s Joker movie starring Joaquin Phoenix, the people from Costumes &amp;amp; Customs has developed a hyperrealistic Joker costume.  That allows you to experience what Phoenix felt when he was performing as the Joker. Without overwhelming success, worldwide recognition, and undisputed wealth. This Halloween you can’t miss the chance to set aside the daily clown costume you call “my job’s uniform”, and replace it with this masterly girl-magnet-different-kind-of-clown costume.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Real-Life Joker Costume comes equipt with everything you need to be in Joker’s skin for a night. This kit includes the whole Joker’s original outfit, a full set of professional makeup with a green-haired wig, and an ensemble of different authentic guns and knives to get the full experience. It also has a CD with a hardcore rock music playlist to listen to while you apply the makeup on your face. Because we know that protecting your masculinity is vital to you. And you can hide the weapons throughout different spots distributed all over the suit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This costume is ideal for all those who want to express how hilarious, yet mysterious they really are. Also, giving you the chance to surprise everyone at the party with some unexpected dance moves, your quirky abrupt and contagious laughter, or killing everyone there when the alcohol runs out. If you’re really a Joker fan, we know you’ll manage to do all three at once! The additional ammo and the character’s charisma sold separately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Halloween is that time of the year to be enjoyed as you please. Kids run and hide all around the neighborhood doing tricks and mischiefs, teenagers have lovely parties where everyone has the same costumes, and everyone gets expired candy. Thanks to the Real Life Joker Costume Kit, the lonely straight men will have the opportunity to drain all of their insecurities and frustrations by committing crimes disguised as the Joker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The positive reception has been so overwhelming that Costumes &amp;amp; Customs is now selling an extra DVD that teaches you to be as real as the costume itself! It has dance lessons with the latest cool moves, a video guide on how to properly use your weapons with torture techniques, and a two hour documentary with descriptions of different traumas and illnesses you can choose from in case you have none.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The demand for this hyper-realistic costume has been staggering. In some cities, there have reported incidents where large groups of men dressed as the Joker start to shoot and stab people in different locations such as movie theaters, shopping malls, and good stand-up comedy shows. Unfortunately, there is no record of people dressed as Batman saving anyone’s life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The increasing crime wave that followed the release of this product is an excellent reflection of the brilliant accuracy of this costume. These Jokers can run freely, having fun, causing mass homicides. Those who bought their outfits from other companies have to conform with the dull Superman attire that can’t even make them fly. Or their Lego character costumes that still won’t make them fit in anywhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Allowing people to become their favorite character instead of just dressing up like them is what makes the work of Costumes &amp;amp; Customs so unique. But this is not the first time the company produced a costume that has turned out so realistic. For example, in the Costumes &amp;amp; Customs catalog, there are other hyperreal disguises. Like a Kylie Jenner costume containing expensive women clothes, an iPod full of “Rise and Shine” remixes with Travis Scott’s entire discography, and a baby girl dol. The costume kit doesn’t come with a father doll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sales of the Real Life Joker Costume are growing with every second. People are starting to get used to the appearances of people dressing up as the Joker, which are not always dangerous but sometimes are somewhat awkward. We asked Randall McCarthy, one of the latest buyers, why he likes this costume so much: “Are you nuts? This costume has given me all I’ve ever needed. If I wear my Joker clothes, people start to notice me. Girls are now laughing at my jokes! And if they don’t, I kill them. Having this disguise compensates having grown without parents, attention, or affection!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Verdict: The Real-Life Joker Costume is out in your favorite stores now! Don’t give up the chance to show people that ignoring you in high school can have serious consequences. Or use it to go to a party. You don’t have to think about it twice, order yours now and finally get a reason to get out of your mother’s basement this Halloween!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>9</name></author><category term="sharkbait" /><summary type="html">We live in a society that loves Halloween. We all could agree that Halloween is easily one of the coolest parts of the year. You are getting free candy from your neighbors for no reason at all, freaking out because you don’t find the perfect idea for your costume this year, parents letting their children play with their friends, at night, with lots of disguised people all around. Michael Jackson’s private heaven. But this year, you don’t have to worry about which one could be the ideal costume for you. Costume &amp;amp; Customs is ready to help you be the laugh of your office’s Halloween Party this October.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Baby Taser Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/baby-taser-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Baby Taser Review" /><published>2019-10-18T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/baby-taser-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/baby-taser-review/">&lt;p&gt;Are you tired of waking up at 3 AM because of the frantic cries of your lovely newborn? Exhausted by pretending that you don’t mind the constant weeping of your beautiful baby twins on that long road trip from Houston to Albuquerque? Fed up with the tough search for a miraculous answer to pacify the unbearable wailing of your angelical children? You don’t have to hide alone in your car to cry because of your miserable existence anymore! The brand-new Baby-Taser has arrived to help parents in need. Fixing your sleep schedule, and possibly save your marriage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Baby Taser doesn’t work as a weapon, but as a tool that assists parents in soothing their children when they unexpectedly start bawling in the most inopportune situations; such as during a long flight, in the middle of your favorite movie, or when your spouse finally wants to get laid. This marvelous product is specifically designed to disrupt the incipient muscle functions of your children in different levels adapted to an infant’s body, meaning it could just calm them down for a while or immediately get them into a gentle sleep. Both using a moderate amount of electric shocks with the same care as a light slap in the face, and without causing any significant physical harm to your baby. Ironically, some inquisitive parents have also discovered that the Baby-Taser can also be set up to quickly wake your toddlers up if you want to spend some quality time with them!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This product has been designed, developed, and distributed by SoftWeaponry TM. Todd N. Truman, the CEO of the company and the genius behind the Baby Taser, took a little time away from his multiple demonstrations and congratulation ceremonies to tell us a little bit about what inspired him to develop this life-changing product: “Well, we were actually working on a special electroshock weapon for aggressive dogs, you know. Back in those days, I used to sleep at my office because my newborn twins used to wake me and my wife up constantly in the middle of the night. One day, after a long meeting we all agreed it would’ve been really cruel to do such a thing to a poor dog, even if it’s out of control. I didn’t know what to do, and at that point, we already spent a lot of money and resources on the product. But that same day, my wife called me while I was clearing my desk for a nap to tell me she was pregnant again. I took one of our prototypes, aimed it to my head and tried to kill myself. Instead of ending my agony, it got me shocked into the sweetest of dreams until my secretary woke me up the next morning, I already had the concept in my head: A Taser for my bab… for babies, in general!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The attractiveness of the Baby Taser goes beyond its simplicity and its effectiveness: It has many pleasing features. The Baby Taser comes in many different presentations such as the classic stun gun and the simple and elegant baton with cartoon prints. There are some more friendly designs with the shape of your children’s favorite characters like Spongebob, Mickey Mouse or Bob Dylan.  If it wasn’t enough, the SoftWeaponry team recently launched a new Elmo-shaped Baby Taser that can be left in your child’s cradle to accompany your baby, sing some lullabies overnight and if your child wakes up for any reason, this sophisticated Baby-Taser will carefully shock them back to sleep while it plays Rock-a-bye Baby.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The acceptance rate of the Baby Taser has been impressively high since its first batch launch. William Silverstone, a single father whose wife passed away one year ago, gave us some feedback about it: “It’s awesome. I mean, I can’t talk for my baby girl but, you know. They fall asleep, how bad can it be? I don’t have to pay for a daycare anymore, I wake up, have my coffee, Baby-Tase my little girl, put her in my suitcase and go to work!”. The numbers are crazy! Stores are selling out of their stock within 72 hours of receiving a shipment. Babysitters are so pleased with this invention that some of them are not charging for their services anymore. They’re are doing it for fun. Studies show that the principal buyers of the Baby Taser are daycare centers, nanny agencies, and single mothers. Many who have also requested SoftWeaponry for products with a longer range and more cadence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite its many advantages and how much it has improved the lives of many, the Baby Taser has naturally received some criticism. When they heard about it, the UN began a study of the product which resulted in a harsh denouncement of the manufacturers for the inhuman, cruel and excessive use of plastic in the fabrication of the product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Baby Taser development team is currently working to deliver a new environmental-friendly line. Also, the PR department of SoftWeaponry has stated that they are constantly receiving letters with complaints asking why they took so long to invent the Baby Taser.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Verdict: Don’t judge the brand-new Baby Taser before trying it. This product is so durable that you can use it for years even into your child’s teens, and even electroshock your unemployed 27-year-old baby from the house once you get tired of them. Don’t miss this chance to be part of a better parenting experience!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>9</name></author><category term="sharkbait" /><summary type="html">Are you tired of waking up at 3 AM because of the frantic cries of your lovely newborn? Exhausted by pretending that you don’t mind the constant weeping of your beautiful baby twins on that long road trip from Houston to Albuquerque? Fed up with the tough search for a miraculous answer to pacify the unbearable wailing of your angelical children? You don’t have to hide alone in your car to cry because of your miserable existence anymore! The brand-new Baby-Taser has arrived to help parents in need. Fixing your sleep schedule, and possibly save your marriage.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Garmin Forerunner Gps Running Watch Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Garmin-Forerunner-GPS-Running-Watch-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Garmin Forerunner Gps Running Watch Review" /><published>2019-10-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Garmin-Forerunner-GPS-Running-Watch-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Garmin-Forerunner-GPS-Running-Watch-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- product brand --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Everyone knows that exercising is excellent for you. The common refrain, “Use it or lose it,” certainly applies to the human form. We live in a sedentary lifestyle inducing world. From our offices where we sit in a chair and work, to our homes where we sit on our couches and play video games or browse through Netflix shows, we usually sit still. This life leads to an increase in health issues and cascades into overall lower quality of life. No one wants that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, most people can do simple exercises like walking or running, which can massively increase their quality of life. Running helps to tone the body and refine the mind. It is something that can minimize daily stress, help with cardiovascular health, and relieve depression. A few experts in the matter even think that running is something that propels humans forward because of its role in our evolution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Running was not in fashion for a while, but it has come back. This is evidenced by the success of the Shoe Dog, people like Phil Knight and his company, Nike. Runners now have a large community, more tools, and an increasing number of tracks to do what they love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if you are planning on joining the running population, a &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; watch might be right for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s find out what this provides to its wearer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; can easily hold up to 500 songs. That’s something that many runners would want to have and can appreciate as they go for their run. Individuals can add a pair of Bluetooth headphones to their purchases to minimize the need for their mobile devices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One fantastic feature might be the fact that you don’t have to be online to listen to music. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; syncs your favorite songs from different streaming providers to allow you to listen offline. Users should note that this might require another premium purchase from the third party music streaming company. Yes, you can connect it to Spotify and download the Spotify app without the need for a smartphone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next feature is for those who like to keep it simple and modern while they shop. The Garmin Pay contactless payment feature lets users pay easily with the Garmin watch. The contactless pay feature works with select companies allowing runners to travel light.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another compelling component of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is the set of running features it provides to its user base. The watch is known for its “advanced running dynamics” that encompasses information such as stride length, and additional information. Through these features, you could get more information on your heart rate and use that to up your running and training game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner 645 Music and GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; watch lasts for quite a while and can work for up to 7 days when using smartwatch mode, and at least 5 hours with GPS mode.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What else can you expect from the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; while you start or continue your quest to build strength, and add psychological value to your life? A sleek design. Users find that the watch can even be passed off as a dressy and more formal watch because of its metal accents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner 645 Music and GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is simple, durable, and made for runners. The watch comes with a simple five-button touch interface that helps you record and keep track of your running workout, and can meet your running needs. Seeing that the watch has a water rating of 5 ATM, runners can also move around in rainy weather so they can always be on the go and take efforts to stay fit and healthy whenever the sky turns the precipitation route&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The watch is optimized for viewing in any type of weather and time of day. If you like to switch things up, replacing bands is simple and time-effective. The company promises that this is one item that doesn’t disappoint in design or durability.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes with GPS/GLONASS, Wi-Fi connectivity, smart notifications, training load, wrist heart rate, Garmin Pay, and music storage. In other words, it has everything you might need while you try to stay active. It weighs only 1.4 ounces and is a delight to wear according to users. It comes with preloaded activities including but not limited to running, treadmill running, biking indoors, and cardio. You will need to keep in mind that 1 CR2 battery is needed with this watch for it to perform its functions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More than 55% of users agree that it is a value buy and that it is well worth the purchase. The people who use this watch range from the tenured runner who follows their set trail every day, to the amateur who just started their running and cardiovascular journey. Those that run for 20-25 miles per week find that the watch proves to meet their stringent needs. Since they don’t want to have to run around with their phones, they would rather have a light device and let it help them in their run - the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a perfect fit for those needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users find that setup is easy and they can quickly input music before heading outdoors. But it might not be as easy for all users if they have never conducted the process of opening up a Garmin account, have not used Garmin Connect, or other components of Garmin.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take note that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has only been tested with a few types of earphones. As such, make sure to look at complimentary headphones (like the Trekz Titanium) to this Garmin watch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Runners find that the watch is a perfect size and that it comes with a fantastic overall design. Nifty features like the vibration alarm do users a great deal of good and help them to wake up on time for their work or running activities. From GPS to running activity, and from display to functionalities like activity tracking, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has helped many users on their running journeys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There have been minimal complaints with the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. It has served many different types of runners who most overwhelmingly support and find significant value in the product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Seeing the positive reviews that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B078H244WN?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Garmin Forerunner GPS Running Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has garnered from users, it might prove to be a good fit for you if you identify as a fitness enthusiast and run on an almost daily basis.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="Garmin Forerunner" /><category term="Watch" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tufts And Needle Queen Mattress Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Tufts-and-Needle-Queen-Mattress-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tufts And Needle Queen Mattress Review" /><published>2019-10-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Tufts-and-Needle-Queen-Mattress-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Tufts-and-Needle-Queen-Mattress-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- product brand --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What is something that you need more of (besides money) and can’t really seem to get enough of each day?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s proper rest and sleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See, sleep is useful in more ways than one and adds significant value to many people’s lives. But the unfortunate reality is that many are quite likely sleep-deprived. Mr T would quite likely pity the increasing number of sleepless people within the world today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sleep allows the mind to rest and relax for the next full day ahead. When one neglects sleep, they prevent their brain from working as efficiently as possible. Because a lot truly happens during times of rest. Even if we don’t know all about the inner workings of our brain, it’s still working for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Did you know that while you sleep, your brain conducts processes that help you store, retain, and utilize the information that can be used in your next full working day?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One can argue that sleep doesn’t only add value to the individual; it adds value to a collective society. When everyone rests well, they can make better decisions that will bring about more progress. Sleep is essential in an increasingly complex world where a good night’s sleep can help enhance problem-solving capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feeling like you’re not creative and as elated as you once were?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A good night’s rest on a &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle Queen Mattress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; might be in the cards for you. Coming home to hit your comfy mattress might be just what you need. By simply resting well, you might find that you can get out of that slump and overall fatigue that’s been accumulating over time, and say hello to a more active and refreshed state of mind with a smile on your face.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not limited to mental rejuvenation either. Proper sleep on a &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle Queen Mattress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; might even help you reduce your physical health problems that range from diabetes to blood pressure, and muscular issues to heart disease.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s take a look at how the widely popular &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle Queen Mattress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; helps people sleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle Queen Mattress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes with adaptive foam. This adaptive foam is said to be important because it emphasizes comfort. The firm incorporates T&amp;amp;N adaptive foam to give users a more flexible yet supportive experience. This provides individuals with the ability to get the rest they need regardless of how they move around in their sleep. Tuft and Needle foam also provides for simple and easy shipping as it is contained in a regular shipping unit and sent to your home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The brand boasts of its superior quality by stepping up its game in terms of materials. They optimize for a fresh and comfortable sleep with the aforementioned T&amp;amp;N Adaptive foam. It’s the T&amp;amp;N Adaptive foam that provides you and your partner a relaxed state of sleep in a convenient manner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The mattress is made up of 2 layers of “a high-density high-quality polyurethane foam” that is checked and certified by a third party known in the bedding industry as CertiPUR-US. As such, &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; can state that they don’t have adverse chemicals or other factors that might be harmful to individuals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users will be happy to note that the mattress was created by scientists with a passion for enhanced sleep. As such, the bed is adaptive and pressure-relieving — further, it’s soft, comfortable, cool, and durable. The brand also pays close attention to the alignment of the spine and neck. The addition of the cooling gel and graphite provides for a better sleeping experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those who are worried about taking on more risk with their purchase, &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; state that they will provide a full refund, in addition to a 100 Night Sleep Trial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further, &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle Queen Mattress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; provide a 10-year limited warranty on this product, allowing for full peace of mind on your part. The company also mentions that users should be aware of one important note, which is that the mattress will take at least 72 hours to progress into its full adaptive form.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users note that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle Queen Mattress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; fits all frames ranging from box springs, slatted frames, and adjustable frames. What’s most compelling for users is the fact that they don’t have to take on any risk, they simply order the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle Queen Mattress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, test it out and return it within 100 days if they don’t like it. They can even order through an authorized reseller like Amazon for simplicity, security, logistics, and free shipping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many users note that this bed will hold up for people who are over the average weight. People who are 6” 4 and weigh 280 pounds have reported that they slept amazingly well with this mattress. More than 70% of customers love this product and rate it very highly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A critical component in the bedding industry is customer service, and the customers of &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; are very happy with the company’s customer service operations. Users note that the customer service listens to their problems and provides them with the help they need. One customer felt that there was more need for firmness and suffered from hip pain. After speaking with the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; customer service team, the customer got a free topper that solved the problem. They didn’t have to wait for a response and were able to resolve their problem promptly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; users note that the bed is comfortable to set up, where one can simply cut the plastic, unroll and let the mattress breathe. They note that factory smell is minimum and isn’t a problem. The localized motion is what many like about the mattress. They don’t have to worry about disturbing their partner or vice versa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, customers feel that they get great value for their money and are overwhelmingly happy with the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B00QBZ265U?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Tufts and Needle Queen Mattress&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. The company minimizes risk with their trial and provides excellent customer service to resolve problems as soon as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are in the market for a new mattress, you might want to give one a try.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="Tufts and Needle" /><category term="Mattress" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Zivix Jamstik Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Zivix-Jamstik-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Zivix Jamstik Review" /><published>2019-10-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Zivix-Jamstik-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Zivix-Jamstik-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- product brand --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Those who enjoy music want to experience it in all its glory. Whether they are listening to their favorite artists through headphones, blasting their favorite tunes on speakers, or jamming their hearts out with friends or family, these different aspects let them get the most out of their music.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While listening to music is quite common and a very affordable hobby, it gets difficult to hold jamming sessions if you don’t have the right equipment with you. But seeing that guitars are expensive and not accessible to everyone, those who want to indulge into jamming often have to leave that plan behind due to lack of resources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a portable, electric guitar, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Zivix Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; claims to make jamming more accessible and playing a guitar more affordable. Sporting a sleek design, the instrument connects to your smartphone, tablet or computer through Bluetooth 4.0. From there, it is all a matter of pairing it up with any compatible MIDI app, and you can emulate the experience of playing a real guitar in the comfort of your home. All of this comes at a very affordable price, which promises to provide great value for money while also paying attention to the quality of music you are about to enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Zivix Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; boasts of real strings and frets that provide the feeling of playing a real guitar. With a Smart Fretboard, it also promises to provide the user with instant feedback to enhance their playing experience. It comes with multiple modes that make playing the guitar more fun for users, whether they are going solo on a practice session or jamming it out with a friend or family member.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Zivix Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is MIDI compatible, which makes it easier to create and mix music with tunes that are produced directly from the guitar device. For those who have not played a guitar before, the device also comes complete with tutorials and games to add to their learning experience. The magnetic pickup technology in the device picks up even the lightest touch and effectively promises to emulate an experience that is as close to playing a real guitar as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The device is available in two packages, with the Black package only having the guitar in it. Whereas, at a slightly higher price, the Case Bundle has a handy travel case or gig bag that lets users carry their guitar around while keeping it safe from dust and grime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Speaking of carrying the guitar around, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Zivix Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; promises to be travel-friendly. Weighing only 1.9lbs with dimensions of 16.5 x 3.5 x 2.5 inches, the device puts portability front and center. But that doesn’t mean that it compromises on design or style by any means. The guitar boasts of a sleek design that is comprised of clean lines, a black frame and silver strings. At the same time, multiple buttons on the side provide additional control to the user. At first look, it is instantly reminiscent of a modernized version of a traditional electric guitar, which is exactly the look that it is going for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes actually to use the guitar, users have found it to be delivering on its promises for the most part. It has been noted that the guitar’s overall functions work as advertised, with its fretboard and strings being quite helpful in composing new tunes while also playing old ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users have noted that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Zivix Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is fairly easy to use, with the connectivity and setting adjustments being an improvement on its predecessor, the original &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. With that, the device also comes with the ability to add multiple &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; to a single device, which paves the way for true to life jamming sessions with friends or family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been noted that the native app for &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is also fairly simple and has an intuitive design, which makes it easy to make adjustments to the device’s sound delivery and play quality. This is especially praised by users who have not used a device like the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; before, or who have simply never had a chance to test the real-world functionality of an actual guitar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The acoustics delivered by &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Zivix Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also earn high praise from those who have used the device. This is possible due to the true to life sound quality that is emulated through the carefully developed strings, fret, and form-factor. Overall, users believe that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is exactly the jamming device they needed to belt out jamming sessions with their loved ones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been noted that the native app for &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is also fairly simple and has an intuitive design, which makes it easy to make adjustments to the device’s sound delivery and play quality. Available for iOS and Android, the app and its functionality is especially praised by users who have not used a device like the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; before, or who have simply never had a chance to test the real-world functionality of an actual guitar.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But seeing that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Zivix Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is specifically built for beginners, this complaint could be brushed aside quite easily. That is why other users have noted that the device fits their needs seamlessly and provides an experience that they had been looking for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Zivix Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a great piece of technology that makes the task of learning to play guitar or simply jamming with likeminded people a more joyful process. If you are someone who is on the learning curve for guitar playing or enjoy busting out the tunes occasionally, then you might find the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B0149YRRXA?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Jamstik+&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; to be a great purchase.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>11</name></author><category term="Zivix Jamstik+" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>