<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-11-13T23:47:39+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">ReviewHuntr.com - The best reviews on the internet.</title><subtitle>ReviewHuntr.com is creating the best reviews on the internet.</subtitle><author><name>ReviewHuntr</name></author><entry><title type="html">Acer Aspire Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Acer-Aspire-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Acer Aspire Review" /><published>2019-11-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-11-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Acer-Aspire-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Acer-Aspire-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- product brand --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07RF1XD36?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Acer Aspire 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a new slim laptop with all of the features and power you need from a standard laptop, in a super thin and lightweight package. The Aspire 5 weighs in at just under five pounds and is shockingly light for its 14-15’’ size. Chock full of different features, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07RF1XD36?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Acer Aspire 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is full of surprises. Within the laptop, you will find an AMD Radeon Vega 3 GPU, an AMD Ryzen 3 dual-core processor, an innovative speaker design utilizing Acer TrueHarmony for deeper and better volume, and a full set of ports. This includes two USB 3 ports, one USB type C port, an HDMI 1 port, and more.
Thin laptops, for the longest time, have essentially been a cheaper option for those who can’t buy a regular laptop. When you consider that laptops are already a cheaper option for those who can’t buy a PC, thin laptops might seem like they can’t hold up when compared with other options. With the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07RF1XD36?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Acer Aspire 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, all of that has changed. While you still won’t be getting PC levels of computing power here, you will be getting an impressively powerful laptop, for a much lower price. Outside of technological aspects, the build of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07RF1XD36?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Acer Aspire&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; itself is quite good for the low price point of only $350. The Aspire 5 has an aluminum frame and is resistant to flexing and bending. When you consider the multiple color options as well, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07RF1XD36?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Acer Aspire 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is great if you want to carry your laptop with you at all times. With its lightweight build, sleek and slim design, thin bezels, and cheap price, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07RF1XD36?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Acer Aspire 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is perfect for people who want to be able to play games or do work on the go. The included AMD Radeon Vega 3 GPU allows for incredibly smooth and speedy gaming and the Ryzen 3 dual-core processor uses less power than some other processors while still allowing for good performance. The battery life on the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07RF1XD36?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Acer Aspire 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is astounding as well, lasting up to 11 hours under some circumstances. Overall the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07RF1XD36?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Acer Aspire 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is an absolute beast for a laptop of its size. 
The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07RF1XD36?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Acer Aspire 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also has the benefit of a very high-quality keyboard, with no soft or mushy keys, and even backlighting. With Acer Color Intelligence, the colors on the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07RF1XD36?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Acer Aspire 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; are vibrant and high quality, and you can work or game for much longer periods in the night with Acer BlueLightShield. With the previously mentioned Acer TrueHarmony, music and other audio come to life on the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07RF1XD36?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Acer Aspire 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. The Aspire 5 is also compatible with both Amazon Alexa and Microsoft Cortana. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07RF1XD36?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Acer Aspire 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is good for gaming, but it shines when it comes to work. Be it for school, university or college, or a job, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07RF1XD36?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Acer Aspire 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has you covered. When working with any kind of software, or when having multiple tabs or programs open at the same time, the Aspire 5 still runs smoothly and quickly. Programs open quickly and run with little to no issue. In addition to that, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07RF1XD36?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Acer Aspire 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is well built for working as well. It manages to have a wide variety of ports while still looking clean and simple from the outside, and there are no fancy overcomplicated designs on the cover or the bottom of the laptop. The Aspire 5 is lightweight and small and can slip right into your backpack with ease and the aluminum cover makes the design stand out while still being aesthetically pleasing. While the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07RF1XD36?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Acer Aspire 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes with a decent 4 gigabytes of ram, it can easily be upgraded to have more if you want. 
The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07RF1XD36?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Acer Aspire 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has a light and stylish build and is thinner than most laptops currently while still performing on par with them. The Aspire 5 has access to a great selection of ports for the price, and still manages to keep a simple aesthetic. It isn’t necessarily the best laptop for gaming and the base RAM size is small, but it can easily be upgraded and can still run most games fairly well. It has a high-quality build with a shockingly good keyboard, even including a backlight. The simple design of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07RF1XD36?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Acer Aspire 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is completed with the premium aluminum cover. Colors and sounds come to life with Acer TrueHarmony and Acer Color Intelligence, and even with all of that, it still manages to run smoothly with almost all software.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07RF1XD36?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Acer Aspire 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is currently one of the best cheap laptops you can get right now, especially if you want to game or work on a budget&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>7</name></author><category term="Acer Aspire" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dji Spark Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/DJI-Spark-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dji Spark Review" /><published>2019-11-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-11-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/DJI-Spark-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/DJI-Spark-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- product brand --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Drones are very cool. Drones like the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B075TDRS2M?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DJI Spark Remote Control Combo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; can be even cooler. Both interesting and entertaining, these types of devices are becoming more important in an era where we expect convenience over everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From small startups to large corporations, some are using drones to deliver packages while others are using them for food delivery. But that’s not all, since drones are also used in the battlefield on a regular basis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simply put, these unmanned aerial vehicles (UAVs) have so many uses besides entertainment that there are many companies who have established a base in this sector. That’s why, the drone industry is likely to keep growing over the next decade. Why won’t it? People ranging from adults to kids love their drones and use them for a broad range of reasons. For them, it will definitely be fun to use these products and learn more about their versatility as they advance further.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s even better is that drone technology will continue to evolve as each different component is improved over time. As more innovation and big investment brings more advanced drones to the market every few months, getting in early and understanding the basics might be worth your time as a drone enthusiast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this in mind, it’s essential that you get in on the drone trend and get a UAV of your own to fly around. It can help you get acclimated with the technology before it gets too late to do so, while also providing you with plenty of fun in the process. Since &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B075TDRS2M?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DJI Spark Remote Control Combo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; promises all that and more, let’s see what it has to offer to its users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B075TDRS2M?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DJI Spark Remote Control Combo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First off, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B075TDRS2M?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DJI Spark Remote Control Combo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes with a remote controller as well as a standard Spark accessory kit. Users will also note that it has a 2-axis stabilized Gimbal Camera that boasts of the ability to take 12 MP still photos while also being able to shoot 1080p Full HD videos. This means that you can take standard quality pictures and videos, which are great for casual and aspiring photographers and videographers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is Easy to Fly&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B075TDRS2M?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DJI Spark Remote Control Combo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes with flight autonomy, GPS and vision position-based navigation, and a 3D obstacle detection system. But what does that even mean for the user? It’s simple. The drone can navigate its way easily through different routes with less chances of bumping into obstacles. This advanced technology adds to the drone’s capabilities and allows it to move about in a smarter fashion. It doesn’t rely on satellite signals but may be enhanced by them. This promises a smarter and easier way to fly your UAV whether you are taking pictures, videos, or simply posing for selfies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It Comes With All Basic Accessories&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The drone comes with three foldable pairs of propellers, which makes it easier to carry around for larger shoots. It also comes with its own Intelligent Spark battery, charger, and micro-USB cable. According to users, these accessories are standard to any drone and help make the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B075TDRS2M?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DJI Spark Remote Control Combo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; be on par with its many counterparts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It Has a Good Speed&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, users note that the drone can go up to at least 31 mph when used in sport mode. It can last for 16 minutes with each charge. According to users, the battery time can fluctuate a couple minutes under the 16 minutes range, but they are satisfied with what time they get out of a single charge anyway.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It Promises Value for Money&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the battery life is decent according to users, the drone does not come with a memory card. This means that you can get ready to spend an additional amount of money on a memory card before you can enjoy taking photos with your drone. But users seem content with this requirement as well, stating that the drone is already cheaper than what it used to be and is currently being offered as a bargain at its current price. For many, the drone promises value for money with its overall features, speed and agility.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from getting positive reviews for its price and overall package, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B075TDRS2M?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DJI Spark Remote Control Combo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also has a control range of up to 1.2 miles. Users find this to be a pretty good control range, since the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B075TDRS2M?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DJI Spark Remote Control Combo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is considered more of a starter drone than anything else by the UAV enthusiasts who have purchased it. According to users, the easy to fly drone presents a good starting point to learn what being a UAV pilot is all about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Dimensions are Pretty Neat&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B075TDRS2M?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DJI Spark Remote Control Combo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; weighs approximately 1.6 lbs and sports the dimensions of 10.2 x 8.5 x 6.6 inches. This makes the drone easier to fly for new pilots, while also giving it a certain edge over bulkier counterparts that come in the same price point. Users find the drone to be easy to carry around, which makes adventure photography more fun for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But Users Have Issues with the GPS Signal&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With that being said, very few users of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B075TDRS2M?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DJI Spark Remote Control Combo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; seem to take issue with the drone’s GPS signal capabilities. Some of these users note that the GPS signal calibration is not very easy, while others mention that the GPS signal is often lost when the drone has not even reached its control range. This makes the drone difficult to fly for these users and causes issues with retrieval to home. At the same time, other users seem perfectly happy with the way they have flown the drone and how it has returned results that they expected out of it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B075TDRS2M?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;DJI Spark Remote Control Combo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; remains a good value for money for its users, especially if you are going to utilize it for home use in terms of some flying fun, or for taking casual pictures and videos. But if you are looking for a more professional drone with higher picture quality and flight time, then looking into another model might be the right choice for you.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>6</name></author><category term=" DJI Spark" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dell Inspiron Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Dell-Inspiron-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dell Inspiron Review" /><published>2019-11-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-11-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Dell-Inspiron-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Dell-Inspiron-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- product brand --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Steve Jobs was right. The computer can serve as a bicycle for the mind. That accelerated function of mind is probably why we live in this era of computing. Yes, it’s indeed clear that it may not be the best era for tech. But it certainly is a pleasant one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Computers are available to most people, and consumers can benefit from Moore’s law and other concepts that have led to modern personal computing as we know it. That’s why, we all have our favorite personal computers and operating systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is no contest that many people prefer Mac over Windows when it comes to personal computing. But for those who tend to go the Windows route for performance and customization, we have got something to talk about today.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07KY83DPV?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dell Inspiron 14 2-in-1 laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And boy, does it promise great value for money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only is it currently at a discounted price but it’s perfect for those who are on the go at work or at school - especially when they are on a budget. Without further ado, let’s find out how the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07KY83DPV?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dell Inspiron 14&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;” holds up against a detailed inspection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, the Specs&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07KY83DPV?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dell Inspiron 14&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is said to be fun and functional. It serves as a 2 in 1 laptop and comes with a grey touch HD cover. It comes with a 14 inch HD screen (1366 X 768). It also boasts of an LED-backlit touch display and an 8th Generation Intel Core i3-8145u processor to boot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The computing unit packs quite a punch with its processor that has 4MB Cache and 3.9 GHz of speed. With the Intel UHD Graphics 620 and shared graphics memory, it provides ample multimedia capabilities in its small size.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07KY83DPV?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dell Inspiron 14&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also has a 128 GB M.2 PCIe Solid State Drive (SSD). Much like most modern laptops, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07KY83DPV?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dell Inspiron 14&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; does away with an optical DVD/CD drive. But it does have a 3-in-1 media card reader, USB 3.0, and USB 2.0 to help users transfer their media files easily. Finally, it also comes with a 3-Cell 42Whr integrated battery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the fun is just getting started with this laptop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It Promises an Enjoyable Multimedia Experience&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s amazing about this laptop is that it brings about a cinematic experience for its users. With less buffering, banging sound quality and crystal clear pictures, it will be hard to regret this purchase. Dell tries to go above and beyond with cinematic color, sound, and stream in most of its machines, and it shows in this particular laptop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users have noted that the laptop meets their performance and storage needs easily. Since the laptop packs an 8th Generation Intel Core i3-8145U processor in addition to its 4GB DDR4 memory, it has plenty of power to carry out multimedia tasks on the go. This means that you can download a substantial amount of software, play games, and enjoy streaming services such as Netflix and the new Disney+ to your heart’s delight. But what else this Dell Inspiron 12 2 in 1 Laptop have to offer?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, its flexibility, of course.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Laptop Offers Flexible Options&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The laptop comes with 4 modes and can be termed as the tech equivalent of being all business in the front but throwing a party in the back. If this brings about a fun image to your mind, then the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07KY83DPV?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dell Inspiron 14&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; might be the perfect match for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With its Windows OS, professionals can utilize it as a basic laptop to get their work done, meeting their number crunching and their presentation needs with ease. But that’s not all that the laptop does.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s also its tablet mode that allows it to be used as a way to thumb through users’ favorite e-books or possibly draw the next digital masterpiece. Users can also check the laptop’s tent and media features to truly dive into the processing power of this machine. The laptop also connects to a TV to project is image onto the big screen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s see what its users say.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s Easy to Set Up&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users seem to be quite satisfied with the setup aspect of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07KY83DPV?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dell Inspiron 14&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. According to them, the process was easy enough in itself. But wherever they seemed to have any difficulties, they were helped through the setup process by the ever-helpful Cortana.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many users mention that browsing and bringing in more applications from the Microsoft store is simple. But going through third party applications through that platform is not as easy as one would want it to be. With that being said, downloading applications directly from the web seems to work as easily as on any other Windows machine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It Strikes a Good Balance Between Features&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to users, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07KY83DPV?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dell Inspiron 14&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has all the latest features of Windows in terms of energy-conserving and touchscreen. The laptop can also handle the simple workload that users have without getting blazingly hot.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users state this might not be a heavy-duty laptop computer for everyone, but it works for basic entertainment needs such as browsing and multimedia consumption. It also works perfectly for simple office tasks. Users mostly agree that it is made for those who want to have a simple device that will perform non-heavy functions. This isn’t going to be a device that will be used for heavy gaming or cryptocurrency mining.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It Has a Few Issues With Connectivity&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Very few users have noted that the computer has some issues when connecting to the internet and when browsing around at first. But they also state that those problems usually get resolved after some time. A few users also lament the fact that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07KY83DPV?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dell Inspiron 14&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; does not come with a bundled DVD player/burner for their different activities. They also note that it doesn’t have an RJ45 port to facilitate direct Ethernet connections to a router.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some users were also expecting to receive premium applications such as Microsoft Office with their purchase. But they were disgruntled to find that they had to pay additionally for them. Since buying MS Office remains a standard understanding among Windows users, this particular issue does not have that much impact on the overall value offering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07KY83DPV?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dell Inspiron 14 2-in-1 laptop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is not made for heavy-duty gamers, miners, or other computer users. It’s there for the everyday individual to browse Facebook, watch Netflix, send emails, and do simple tasks that range from writing to reading. Most users are happy with what the laptop offers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One user said it best, it is a jack of all trades but a master of none.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the time of writing, the laptop is also available at a discounted price. For what it’s worth, checking out what it has to offer may just pair you up with the basic machine you want for everyday tasks.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>6</name></author><category term="Dell Inspiron" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Gravity Blanket Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Gravity-Blanket-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Gravity Blanket Review" /><published>2019-11-13T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-11-13T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Gravity-Blanket-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Gravity-Blanket-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- product brand --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sleep. Everyone wants and needs it, but only a specific percentage of the population actually gets it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who knows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d wager that our lack of sleep may be due to our fascination with our devices, and the blue light emanating from our screens. Insomnia may also be a cause of our hectic work schedules, which may prevent us from a sound sleep. Whatever the case may be, we all know that fantastic sleep helps us to think, act, and perform better overall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Me? I’m a big fan of sleep. I think sleep is a time to slow all the way down in an increasingly fast-paced world. Our time of hibernation provides us with the opportunity to rest, relax, and give ourselves a break.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That’s why I started looking into products that might improve and enhance my sleeping experience. I heard about the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity Blanket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: The Weighted Blanket for Sleep, Stress, and Anxiety sometime ago when they did their Kickstarter campaign, but I didn’t really pay too much attention to it. Since I’m more focused on sleep now, I figured I’d take a look at the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity Blanket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: The Weighted Blanket for Sleep, Stress, and Anxiety and see what it was all about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity Blanket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is especially intriguing because it is supposed to be a “premium-grade weighted blanket” that helps with stress, and anxiety. It helps to improve sleep and minimizes stress and anxiety. It improves the cycle of rapid eye movement (REM) sleep while increasing serotonin and melatonin and is said to feel amazing. What’s not to love?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity Blanket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;: The Weighted Blanket For Sleep, Stress, and Anxiety&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The company states that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity Blanket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; was created with your satisfaction and comfort in mind. From features such as an ultra-soft duvet cover to the additions of enclosed glass beads, the blanket is supposed to revolutionize your sleep experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But does it really?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let’s talk about the specifications and the overall make of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity Blanket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One can purchase the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity Blanket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; in several weights, 15 pounds, 20 pounds, and 25 pounds. The company recommends &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; sleepers to buy blanket weights that are about 10% of one’s body weight.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity Blanket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes in one size 72” x 48”. It’s not supposed to be for two people, just one. The idea is that an individual will feel maximum comfort when they cover themselves with the blanket. The weighted distribution of the blanket that encompasses the body of the individual is where the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; magic happens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So it is essential to remember not to share this blanket, lest ye sacrifice thine comfort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But how is the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity Blanket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; made?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; states that the blanket’s exterior is comprised of extra “soft micro-fleece.” Its internal weighted layer is comprised of cotton and weighted beads. This inner layer is held securely by ties and elastic-button straps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How must you care for the blanket? It’s simple. Machine wash the exterior but be gentle, and hand wash the interior.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The blanket comes in two colors, navy and space grey. But most people go with space grey probably because it just looks cooler.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, that we’ve got the basics covered, let’s take a look at the feedback on the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity Blanket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s What People Love about the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity Blanket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;s&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most people think that it is a fantastic blanket that’s amazingly soft and cozy. Users also find that it serves its purpose as a weighted blanket, helping them sleep like a baby. They have also seen that it does make them feel more secure, and it increases their comfort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many are right in line with the fact that the blanket is only made for one person, so those who loved it purchased one for their significant other. Users with a reported problem of a lack of proper sleep, especially those who previously had less than 3 hours of sleep at night note that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity Blanket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has helped them sleep for more than 5 hours regularly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People have also used it in a variety of places, on the bed, on the couch, and chairs as well. Those that really love the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity Blanket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;s provide one bit of caution, you might not ever want to leave your bed. With it, users are also pleased with the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; customer service team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The product does work as generally advertised, but there have been a few recurring drawbacks with the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity Blanket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s What People Hate about the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity Blanket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;s&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Blanket is Said to Be Too Hot&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many talk about the fact that these &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity Blanket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;s are too hot. Too much heat leads to sweating. Sweating leads to uncomfortable sleep, and restless sleep leads to unhappy people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But fear not, there’s a solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users have resolved this problem in several ways. For one, they have turned down the temperature in their rooms and/or placed another blanket between themselves and the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity Blanket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. It is important to remember that depending upon your body temperature, you might feel that the blanket is a bit too warm and might need to do as those who have faced these similar problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It Reportedly Has Uneven Weight Distribution&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users note that the blanket has the weight, but it feels as if all the weight goes to the sides of the blanket. This may seem like a significant problem because the whole point of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity Blanket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is to provide users with that sensational cozy, hugged, and snug feel. Without the proper distribution of weight, the blanket might turn out to be more of a hassle and may not meet users’ expectations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It Has Shown Inconsistent Quality to a Few Users&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some users say that the product as inconsistencies in quality. A few users purchased several blankets and experienced a difference in quality. While some of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity Blanket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;s have stayed true and durable over time, others have a smaller use life. Issues such as the poor quality of the threads on coverlets, beads congregating on one side of the blanket, and other problems are a concern among a small portion of the users. With that being said, most users swear by the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity Blanket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; and mention that it has provided them with no issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Price is High - But Now There’s a Discount&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users who purchased it at the original price feel that they overpaid. According to them, they would have been more comfortable with the product if they bought it a discount.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the time of writing, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity Blanket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is available at a steep discount, which helps in resolving this argument.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity Blanket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; works really well for some and not so well for others. Users with different bodies (temperatures, weight, and height) react differently to the blanket. Most people love it and would purchase the product. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07BN75Z3R?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gravity Blanket&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is currently at a steep discount and has all the potential to act as a valued purchase for most people.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>6</name></author><category term=" Gravity Blanket" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Apple Watch Series Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Apple-Watch-Series-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Apple Watch Series Review" /><published>2019-11-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-11-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Apple-Watch-Series-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Apple-Watch-Series-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- product brand --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A smartwatch often provides a simple and easy way to stay connected without needing to pick up your phone, allowing you to answer calls and check your notifications quickly. They are also particularly useful if you want to track your workout routines and any progress towards a fitness goal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They compact everything you need from your phone, but in a more discreet and professional design, ideal for starting and ending meetings on time and returning calls promptly without constantly interrupting work in progress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most recent addition to this line of devices is the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07XQSJ7Q5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Apple Watch Series 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. Apple Watches are known for using a wireless connection to an iPhone to perform functions such as calling and texting and can also connect to Wi-Fi network for additional tasks. However, since Series 3 and later LTE Apple Watches can independently connect to a mobile network, bypassing the need for an iPhone after their initial setup. This is a huge improvement, as it allows the user to work separately from their phones, making for a more independent device.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This best-selling wearable device includes an always-on display with energy-saving OLED screen and low-power screen driver capable of refresh rates as low as once per second. Additional new features include International Emergency Calling enabling emergency calls in over 150 countries, a more power-efficient S5 processor, improved ambient sensor, doubling of storage to 32GB, and the addition of a magnetometer, which enables a compass function useful for traveling and hiking trips.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the main advantages of an &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07XQSJ7Q5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Apple Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is Siri. Having easy access to an assistant is amazing. With an &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07XQSJ7Q5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Apple Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; you’ll be able to ask Siri for anything you might need, be it the weather, setting an alarm, or even multiple commands, and it’ll be done in the blink of an eye. Pairing an &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07XQSJ7Q5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Apple Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; with a home kit can be particularly useful, and it will help you automate multiple tasks simply with a voice command. Home kits range from locks to speakers, smart plugs or even light strips that can be controlled easily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second advantage of an &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07XQSJ7Q5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Apple Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is organization. You’ll have your calendar, meetings, timers, and access to different time zones, all so you can correctly plan and distribute your tasks throughout the day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07XQSJ7Q5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Apple Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; can also be customized to suit your needs. You can change the watch band and it’ll feel like having a new watch altogether, as the different designs can go from classy to casual or sport. Changing the watch face is very simple, and it’ll help you display the information you consider necessary, all with one touch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07XQSJ7Q5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Apple Watch Series 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; received positive reviews, reaching a promising rating of 4.5 stars out of 5 on Amazon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On this device, the users have commented about the band, which is sturdy and strong but without being rigid or uncomfortable. The design and build quality have been praised, as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Purchasers have found Apple Watch’s ability to track sleep, heart rate and calories very useful. Others have found this device very practical when walking their dog, as this smartwatch foregoes the need for a phone, and it’s easier to use when dealing with a leash or busy hands.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Series 5 seems to be a big upgrade when compared to its predecessors. The slightly bigger screen has been accepted positively and new features such as cellular and Wi-Fi have been considered a major improvement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When reading the negative reviews, the biggest complaint was that this smartwatch needs to be activated via an iPhone before its first use. Some users experienced troubles when activating it, while others said it’s very easy to set up and sync with an iPhone. So in this topic, it seems to be more of a technical issue than a problem with the smartwatch itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some said that the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07XQSJ7Q5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Apple Watch Series 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is by far the best version of &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07XQSJ7Q5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Apple Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; yet. The always-on display has received favorable reviews, and it’s said that it brings the smartwatch closer to an actual watch. With this new addition, the screen stays always on but dims slightly when your wrist is turned away from you. 
This feature can be turned off if the user would rather not have the screen always lit. However, the always-on can be useful when you need to glance at the time without having to wake it up, as it would be in a meeting or a professional setting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The battery life is said to have vastly improved over previous versions, even with the always-on feature turned on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users had a positive surprise with the quality of the speaker. According to some reviewers, it sounds just like the iPhone 11 Pro speaker, very clear and with a wide range for lower and higher frequencies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Users commented that the screen auto-adjusts to light better than previous generations and that the ECG sensor is particularly good and accurate, which makes this smartwatch ideal for tracking general daily activities and workouts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Series 5 has 32GB of storage versus 16GB on the Series 3, this means more space for music, podcasts or apps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what’s been undoubtedly most praised are the improvements to the LTE version and the way it connects to AT&amp;amp;T network, which allows you to leave your phone behind. This makes the Series 5 a worthy upgrade from an &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07XQSJ7Q5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Apple Watch&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; Series 3. In previous non-LTE versions, the phone connects to your iPhone via Bluetooth so you have to be within 25 feet of your phone to sync). Because of this, users had to always keep their phone close, which defeated the purpose of having a smartwatch. The LTE version helps you reduce screen time, as you can leave your phone home without the fear missing out on an important phone call or text.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07XQSJ7Q5?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Apple Watch Series 5&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a device you won’t regret purchasing, given its multiple uses and how versatile it can be. Some users go as far as to call it “the best smartwatch ever.”&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>5</name></author><category term="Apple Watch" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Razer Phone Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Razer-Phone-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Razer Phone Review" /><published>2019-11-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-11-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Razer-Phone-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Razer-Phone-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- product brand --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mobile phones have been catered towards the mainstream market since their inception, but today gamers and power-hungry enthusiasts can rejoice. The all-new &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is packed with cutting edge hardware and sophisticated software. With enough power to make any mobile gamer drool, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; hits the sweet spot in regards to price and performance. Coming in at just shy of 400$, it’s much cheaper than the latest thousand dollar iPhones.
Overall, the phone is built with a fairly premium feel. You can opt for a matte black finish, or go with the regal satin finish. The phone has one of the best displays on the market, and hardware to match it. The phone also has Razer’s innovative Chroma software for all your lighting needs. The phone comes with android 9, and a free version of the acclaimed Nova Launcher. The dual front-facing speakers are super loud and feature Dolby’s Atmos technology, which seeks to enhance mobile audio for specific use cases. Overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a solid phone, and ill be getting into the specifics in the next section.
 The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has one of the best displays of any mobile phone. A 120Hz panel allows you to experience ultra-high refresh rate gaming. Most of you are probably reading this review on a standard 60Hz monitor, half as fast as the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;’s panel. Coming in at around 5.72 inches, it’s not a small display by any means. Gorilla Glass 5 ensures your phone safety, being rated to survive a 1.6m fall 80% of the time. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; truly has a world-class display.
 Most people buy this phone for gaming and it doesn’t disappoint at all in that department. If you’re looking for crisp audio to any headset, the onboard USB-C DAC port will give you high fidelity 24-bit audio. If you’re a speaker person, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; won’t disappoint. Dual front-facing speakers provide clean audio, and Dolby Atmos ensures it caters to your use case. If you’re listening to music or talking with friends, Atmos will cater to your needs. The Qualcomm Snapdragon 845 this phone comes with provides the power you need to tackle even the most graphically demanding games. From PUBG to Fortnite, you can be sure you’ll be running them at the highest graphical presets. An onboard vapour chamber provides efficient cooling for this powerful processor. Graphics matter and the Adreno 630 GPU was born to deliver them. Being one of the fastest mobile GPUs in existence, it crushes and mobile game at any setting. Overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; lives and breathes gaming.
 Battery life is important, especially so when you are gaming. Imagine being in a 1v1 situation in your favourite battle total game, only for your phone to power off from the low battery life of your generic phone. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; packs a 4,000mAh battery, enough to easily go through a full day of demanding usage. The USB-C port allows you to charge your phone in no time at all. Powering the powerful display and CPU is no small task, and the battery delivers with flying colours. Few users have any complaints about the impressive battery.
 Memory is something that mobile gamers often overlook, but it matters nonetheless. Modern games are now always a few gigabytes, so it’s important to have space for them. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has a comfortable 64 Gigabytes of UFS storage. This isn’t as big as some of the modern flagships, but the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has a trick up its sleeve. It features a micro SD slot that can hold up to 1 Terabyte of flash memory. Aside from storage, RAM is also important in terms of memory. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes with a nice 8GB of LPDDR4X of RAM, more than enough to comfortably multitask and play games. 
 Gamers aren’t the type of people who require an amazing camera, but Razer still delivered in this department. The front camera is a decent 8MP one, recording up to 1080p video. This isn’t super cutting edge but more of a nice to have feature. The rear camera, however, is a completely different story. It has a dual-camera setup with image stabilization built-in. The first camera is a stabilized 12MP wide shot lens. The second one is a telephoto with a 12MP sensor. The dual-tone flash makes night time pictures a breeze. You can record video up to 4k, fairly impressive in a gaming phone like this. Overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07H9V6PHZ?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Phone 2&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; packs a good camera on a phone that didn’t even need it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, this is an amazing phone catered mostly to gamers. It’s feature-rich and allows you all the comforts of a flagship for a fraction of the price. A 4-star rating on Amazon is nothing to scoff at either.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>7</name></author><category term="Razer" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Razer Huntsman Elite Gaming Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Razer-Huntsman-Elite-Gaming-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Razer Huntsman Elite Gaming Review" /><published>2019-11-10T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-11-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Razer-Huntsman-Elite-Gaming-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/Razer-Huntsman-Elite-Gaming-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- product brand --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mechanical keyboards are the pinnacle of typing technology, combining design and functionality into a single product. Mechanical Keyboards have been around for decades now, but the rise of gaming has caused an influx of demand in the community. Nowadays, a good quality mechanical keyboard is the standard for gaming and oftentimes, office work. Whether you type for work or recreation, this keyboard will take your abilities to the next level. Combining some of the latest hardware on the market with some of the most robust software on the planet, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is the perfect keyboard for anyone.
   So you may be wondering, what is a mechanical keyboard? Well, I’d be happy to enlighten you. The Keyboard you probably own right now is a traditional rubber dome keyboard, with a simple rubbery feel on each click. What sets the mechanical keyboard apart is that each button has its own switch that generates a satisfying click. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; holds up to the quality Mechanical keyboards come with, having a very durable body and a professionally braided cable. The body is made of premium aluminium and covered with a matte finish. Overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; holds up to many of the stereotypical Mechanical Keyboard expectations.
   The most defining feature of the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is its Opto-Mechanical key switches. Normal mechanical keyboards press on a key switch which goes on to inform the computer about the keypress. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;, however, uses light to further increase the input speed. A sensor inside each key switch detects if a key has been pressed by being activated from an internal laser. Essentially, you are typing at the speed of light! The enhanced key switch is rated to survive up to 100 million keystrokes, double the industry standard. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also has 3 dedicated and tactile media control keys that are sure to grab anyone’s attention. These knobs allow for quick and efficient control over any media you could imagine. From music volume to skipping tracks, it can all be done on your keyboard. Overall, the key switches on the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; make it stand out in front of competitors, and truly define this incredible product.
   You may be wondering who exactly this keyboard is for, and the answer is everyone. Even though it is heavily marketed towards gamers, using a comfy mechanical keyboard on those long office hours will improve your mood and efficiency. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; lets you type a fair but faster, so you will no doubt enjoy it. For gaming, this keyboard delivers anything you could need. Quick macros allow for you to instantly act out difficult key combos in your favourite MMO. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; packs a 10 key rollover, so it can register up to 10 keys at once. This is perfect for those of us who love multi-key key binds. Overall, this keyboard is good for just about anyone.
   Razer Chroma is one of the most customizable lighting platforms anywhere. Through the backlighting on your keyboard and wrist rest, you can make incredible light effects. From, having custom effects for every game to syncing your smart lights, Chroma can transfer your whole room into the game. You can even use the hundreds of premade effects available in Chroma Studio made by users like you. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has 38 different lighting zones that you can edit to your heart’s content, the wrist rest has LED underglow, so you can illuminate every inch of your desk.
   Razer Synapse is a powerful macro tool that can turn the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; into a gaming beast. You can make key-binds to simultaneously press up to 50 keys. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; also has onboard storage, so your macros will be available on any computer you plug it into. This saves time at tournaments where you want to bring your own macros. A special key exists to enable gaming mode, giving you the options to disable the Windows key and the infamous Alt+F4 command. Never worry about pressing the wrong key again. Furthermore, Razer hypershift allows you to access another full set of keys with the press of a single key. This keyboard truly has it all for gamers.
   We all know that Mechanical Keyboards are only meant for PC’s, but Razer has destroyed that notion with the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;. You can now plug your &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; into any Xbox One and use it for basic input. This transforms the traditional notion and adds even more to the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;’s appeal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07DHNX18W?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Razer Huntsman Elite Gaming&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a superb example of what money can buy you these days. A top-notch and cutting edge mechanical keyboard with powerful software to go along with it. It deserves its 4.4-star rating on Amazon.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>7</name></author><category term="Razer" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Evga Geforce Rtx 2080 Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/EVGA-GeForce-RTX-2080-Review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Evga Geforce Rtx 2080 Review" /><published>2019-11-03T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-11-03T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/EVGA-GeForce-RTX-2080-Review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/EVGA-GeForce-RTX-2080-Review/">&lt;!-- product name --&gt;
&lt;!-- product asin --&gt;
&lt;!-- product brand --&gt;
&lt;!-- Amazon url --&gt;
&lt;!-- product full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with full name --&gt;
&lt;!-- link with short name --&gt;
&lt;!-- grabs the first image from the imgs to use as a header --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07N889XT8?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;EVGA GeForce RTX 2080&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a top of the line graphics card, offering robust performance for gamers and content creators alike. It is one of the few graphics cards on the market that can truly handle the demands of nearly any workload. Combined with AI-powered Ray-Tracing technology, it has unmatched performance. This &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07N889XT8?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;GeForce RTX 2080&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; edition comes with pre-installed water cooling, so all you need to do is plug it into your array. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07N889XT8?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;EVGA GeForce RTX 2080&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; truly offers a one-size-fits-all solution in the difficult to navigate the world of graphics cards. It has an impressive 3.7 stars on Amazon, so you’ll be sure to get a functional and powerful product. &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07N889XT8?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;GeForce RTX 2080&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is an industry leader in terms of computer hardware, being one of the largest companies in the scene. I’ll be going through the technical specifications of this product and the workload it can handle, the advanced Ray-Tracing capabilities it comes pre-loaded with, and lastly the different uses it has. Let’s get right into the review!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07N889XT8?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;EVGA GeForce RTX 2080&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; can truly handle any workload, from content creation to gaming. Its robust specifications showcase that, and most users agree upon its unparalleled versatility. Most users purchase this card for gaming, as that’s the user base &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07N889XT8?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;GeForce RTX 2080&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; most often markets its products for. There are no complaints about its performance and versatility. Many users say that during demanding usage, the temperatures can get fairly high. Most users report peaks of 85-86 degrees celsius, which is fairly hot. However, using the water cooling this card was engineered to bring temperatures down to a much more favourable state. Overall, this card can handle nearly all workloads thrown at it easily when matched with popper cooling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Specifications are what matters in our performance-hungry modern world games. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07N889XT8?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;EVGA GeForce RTX 2080&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; comes packed with 8GB of GDDR6 RAM, one of the fastest video memory types in the world. This RAM runs at a blazing fast 14,000 MHz memory speed, capable of storing and retrieving information at a nearly unheard of rate. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07N889XT8?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;EVGA GeForce RTX 2080&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; has am 1800Mhz boost clock, extremely fast! This card definitely packs a punch, and can definitely handle nearly anything. In the next section, ill be talking about this card’s most revered feature, Ray-Tracing. This card in specific has built-in water cooling support, so all you have to do is plug it into your current loop. This is a lot easier than having to add a water cooling block as some cards require. The all-metal backplate provides a premium feel and enhances the cards overall structural integrity. The &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07N889XT8?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;EVGA GeForce RTX 2080&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; supports Nvidia G-Sync so you can experience truly smooth gameplay on compatible monitors. The built-in DisplayPort 1.4 and HDMI 2.0 ports are some of the most powerful modern graphical ports. NVIDIA GPU Boost technology is present in this card, allowing you to push your cards to the limit. This card also has an 8-phase power supply to keep your card safe in the event of a power surge or power loss. The built-in 9-blade dual-fan array is more than enough to keep your system cool. Adjustable RGB LED’s add to the card’s gamer aesthetic, leaving a lasting impression on those that view your rig. No user has a complaint regarding the card’s specifications, so you can rest assured you will have a well built and powerful product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ray-Tracing is an extremely advanced processing platform that can analyze environments in real-time and trace lighting to effectively achieve a nearly photo-realistic environment. Graphics cards with Ray-Tracing can perform up to 6X faster and are powered with AI analysis techniques. This cutting edge technology is easily the most powerful processing technique on the market, effectively tracing every ray of light to provide a picture-perfect image. Ray-Tracing also allows content-creators to run vivid simulations for further scrutiny. Ray-Tracing is a huge plus when purchasing a graphics card, and you’re certainly in luck here with the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07N889XT8?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;EVGA GeForce RTX 2080&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gaming is what most people buy this card for, and it definitely holds up. Most users can effortlessly run their favourite games in 4K resolution at the heights of settings. The unprecedented power of this card has pressed many gaming studios to innovate further in their graphics field. Ray-Tracing is finally being adopted in the gaming industry, something they will finally utilize the full power of this card/ Not a single user has had a complaint about its performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, the &lt;span&gt;&lt;a class=&quot;product-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/dp/B07N889XT8?tag=reviewhuntr-20&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;EVGA GeForce RTX 2080&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; is a super graphics card no matter your need. It has all the power you could ever want and has some of the most cutting edge features on the market. Few users have any complaints about this product, so you can be sure you are getting a high-quality product. It is definitely deserving of its 3.7-star rating on Amazon.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>7</name></author><category term="EVGA GeForce" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Facebook Voting Machines Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/facebook-voting-machines-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Facebook Voting Machines Review" /><published>2019-11-01T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-11-01T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/facebook-voting-machines-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/facebook-voting-machines-review/">&lt;p&gt;Just in time for a fresh election cycle, a new tech startup says it finally holds the solution to foreign interference in American elections. Nootrusha has invented voting machines powered by Facebook with plans to use the technology in critical state and local government elections. We had an opportunity to learn more about these new machines from lead designer Джон Smith. “We are very pleased to start testing them in the field. There are many important choices ahead. People lose confidence in the system with all these reports of election hacking. The decision looked us all this time in the face. By making the process less obvious, we can help restore this confidence in the election.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These new IoT connected voting machines take voting technology a quantum leap into the future. With never before seen conveniences, features, and security measures. You might need sunglasses when you checkout out the bright new 4k OLED touchscreens that display inspirational messages such as “OBEY”, “CONSUME”, and “CONFORM”. Security is an ever-growing concern in the new digital age, and Nootrusha has added features like facial recognition, non-invasive infrared retinal test, and rectal scanning to help assure nobody can steal your identity or vote. For those that feel the new security measures have the potential for abuse, Джон notes that there are also super cool filters that transform your face in real-time. A cute puppy nose and ears, The Mask from the 1994 hit movie The Mask starring Jim Carrey, and dark mode Justin Trudeau are some of the most popular choices in their usability testing. Nootrusha says they have many more in development with the hopes they’ll be ready for the field trials. A “flappy ears” filter in honor of Ross Perot with a toggle that changes them to Barak Obama. And there’s also the limited edition “stained dress” filter by Monica Lewinsky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nootrusha thinks the updates in their design will help make voting more appealing to younger demographics, which historically have a substantially lower turnout in elections despite being unhappy about the current state of like - everything. Jenny from Fort Lauderdale, Florida, had a lot of praise for the new voting machines. “This is so awesome! I love that it let me register with Facebook. And at first, the security stuff had me worried, but then I turned on the Drake filter, AND I HAD DRAKE’S BEARD WITH A GRILL. It was sooooo yeet. And the auto voting feature is a lifesaver. I tried to look up some of the names, but none of them showed up in Spotify. All I had to do was auto-vote, and it did the rest! It even let me share my Drake selfie on Instagram.”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Джон says the new auto-voting option helps streamline the voting process more efficiently than any other solutions available on the market. Джон added, “Companies already track all of your personal information and manipulate your entire existence to influence your decisions. Most people can’t afford free will, and being informed isn’t practical. We’ve managed to streamline the process. We can analyze your social media account to make the same decisions that you would have made yourself. Of course, the more often you use Facebook, the more accurate the results will be. Therefore, we strongly recommend that voters spend as much time using the app as possible. Your Facebook app usage might even be a great measure of patriotism when we expand the program”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He went on to explain how the auto-voting feature uses proprietary machine learning and artificial intelligence algorithms to determine the selections it makes for you. “First, we take all of the content that you and your friends share on social media and completely filter them out of the data. We do this to prevent personal bias impacting the results. That leaves us mostly with advertisements, but it’s good enough. Based on that content, we can easily choose the candidates you will resonate with the most. It could be the latest elderly jingoist running for president or some new up and coming representative with grand ideas for change and few plans to practically see them through. The system is very flexible and responds well across the political spectrum. We are helping voters spend more time relishing in the election spectacles and less time worrying about where their vote goes.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not everyone is excited about the changes, though. A representative from Mosourri’s 7th district says the new Facebook integration in the voting machines poses a danger for young voters. “We already have plenty of ways to mislead, I mean, inform voters. TV, radio, and newspapers have worked perfectly fine for decades. Mr. Facebook has no business trying to get inside the machines we use to vote. And as concerned parents, we’re confident these social media trends will go away if we can make them illegal. They encourage kids to spend too much time on their smartphones instead of watching TV or reading newspapers. We shouldn’t allow it. There’s enormous potential for abuse. Why isn’t anyone thinking of the children?! What if foreign influences start taking advantage of young impressionable voters before we do? Even worse, these social medias are hurting our local economy and continue to disrupt important businesses. Our only newspaper shut down earlier this year, and they were the primary supporter of my campaign. They’ve been advising me since the beginning. How am I supposed to know what laws I should pass now? Americans everywhere should be outraged that these techno loonies are opening a pandora’s box of harm to the very fabric of our country.”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There hasn’t been a lot of reaction to the representative’s warnings since he doesn’t have a Facebook account to share them. Still, others who aren’t super lame have raised similar concerns with the technology. But Джон assures everyone that their tech is developed right here in the heartland of America, Silicon Valley, to help Americans remove all the stressful parts of the election season. Allowing them to focus on the parts of it they love. Джон handed us a laser pointer which projected an image of the United States seal with the eagle modified to include a large erect cock and balls. He then drank from a flask of what smelled like vodka and took an uncomfortably long drag from his cigarette.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Джон hopes to see their efforts help to restore peoples faith in elections, without really changing anything.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>0</name></author><category term="sharkbait" /><summary type="html">Just in time for a fresh election cycle, a new tech startup says it finally holds the solution to foreign interference in American elections. Nootrusha has invented voting machines powered by Facebook with plans to use the technology in critical state and local government elections. We had an opportunity to learn more about these new machines from lead designer Джон Smith. “We are very pleased to start testing them in the field. There are many important choices ahead. People lose confidence in the system with all these reports of election hacking. The decision looked us all this time in the face. By making the process less obvious, we can help restore this confidence in the election.”</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Real Life Joker Costume Review</title><link href="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/real-life-joker-costume-review/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Real Life Joker Costume Review" /><published>2019-10-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2019-10-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/real-life-joker-costume-review</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://reviewhuntr.com/reviews/real-life-joker-costume-review/">&lt;p&gt;We live in a society that loves Halloween. We all could agree that Halloween is easily one of the coolest parts of the year. You are getting free candy from your neighbors for no reason at all, freaking out because you don’t find the perfect idea for your costume this year, parents letting their children play with their friends, at night, with lots of disguised people all around. Michael Jackson’s private heaven. But this year, you don’t have to worry about which one could be the ideal costume for you. Costume &amp;amp; Customs is ready to help you be the laugh of your office’s Halloween Party this October.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the world’s most highly regarded costume designer and manufacturer brings you the brand new Real Life Joker Costume Equipment. Taking advantage of the popularity of this year’s Joker movie starring Joaquin Phoenix, the people from Costumes &amp;amp; Customs has developed a hyperrealistic Joker costume.  That allows you to experience what Phoenix felt when he was performing as the Joker. Without overwhelming success, worldwide recognition, and undisputed wealth. This Halloween you can’t miss the chance to set aside the daily clown costume you call “my job’s uniform”, and replace it with this masterly girl-magnet-different-kind-of-clown costume.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Real-Life Joker Costume comes equipt with everything you need to be in Joker’s skin for a night. This kit includes the whole Joker’s original outfit, a full set of professional makeup with a green-haired wig, and an ensemble of different authentic guns and knives to get the full experience. It also has a CD with a hardcore rock music playlist to listen to while you apply the makeup on your face. Because we know that protecting your masculinity is vital to you. And you can hide the weapons throughout different spots distributed all over the suit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This costume is ideal for all those who want to express how hilarious, yet mysterious they really are. Also, giving you the chance to surprise everyone at the party with some unexpected dance moves, your quirky abrupt and contagious laughter, or killing everyone there when the alcohol runs out. If you’re really a Joker fan, we know you’ll manage to do all three at once! The additional ammo and the character’s charisma sold separately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Halloween is that time of the year to be enjoyed as you please. Kids run and hide all around the neighborhood doing tricks and mischiefs, teenagers have lovely parties where everyone has the same costumes, and everyone gets expired candy. Thanks to the Real Life Joker Costume Kit, the lonely straight men will have the opportunity to drain all of their insecurities and frustrations by committing crimes disguised as the Joker.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The positive reception has been so overwhelming that Costumes &amp;amp; Customs is now selling an extra DVD that teaches you to be as real as the costume itself! It has dance lessons with the latest cool moves, a video guide on how to properly use your weapons with torture techniques, and a two hour documentary with descriptions of different traumas and illnesses you can choose from in case you have none.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The demand for this hyper-realistic costume has been staggering. In some cities, there have reported incidents where large groups of men dressed as the Joker start to shoot and stab people in different locations such as movie theaters, shopping malls, and good stand-up comedy shows. Unfortunately, there is no record of people dressed as Batman saving anyone’s life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The increasing crime wave that followed the release of this product is an excellent reflection of the brilliant accuracy of this costume. These Jokers can run freely, having fun, causing mass homicides. Those who bought their outfits from other companies have to conform with the dull Superman attire that can’t even make them fly. Or their Lego character costumes that still won’t make them fit in anywhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Allowing people to become their favorite character instead of just dressing up like them is what makes the work of Costumes &amp;amp; Customs so unique. But this is not the first time the company produced a costume that has turned out so realistic. For example, in the Costumes &amp;amp; Customs catalog, there are other hyperreal disguises. Like a Kylie Jenner costume containing expensive women clothes, an iPod full of “Rise and Shine” remixes with Travis Scott’s entire discography, and a baby girl dol. The costume kit doesn’t come with a father doll.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The sales of the Real Life Joker Costume are growing with every second. People are starting to get used to the appearances of people dressing up as the Joker, which are not always dangerous but sometimes are somewhat awkward. We asked Randall McCarthy, one of the latest buyers, why he likes this costume so much: “Are you nuts? This costume has given me all I’ve ever needed. If I wear my Joker clothes, people start to notice me. Girls are now laughing at my jokes! And if they don’t, I kill them. Having this disguise compensates having grown without parents, attention, or affection!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Verdict: The Real-Life Joker Costume is out in your favorite stores now! Don’t give up the chance to show people that ignoring you in high school can have serious consequences. Or use it to go to a party. You don’t have to think about it twice, order yours now and finally get a reason to get out of your mother’s basement this Halloween!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>9</name></author><category term="sharkbait" /><summary type="html">We live in a society that loves Halloween. We all could agree that Halloween is easily one of the coolest parts of the year. You are getting free candy from your neighbors for no reason at all, freaking out because you don’t find the perfect idea for your costume this year, parents letting their children play with their friends, at night, with lots of disguised people all around. Michael Jackson’s private heaven. But this year, you don’t have to worry about which one could be the ideal costume for you. Costume &amp;amp; Customs is ready to help you be the laugh of your office’s Halloween Party this October.</summary></entry></feed>